You said,
if I hadn't set up a trap
to lure him into revealing himself,
would my father still be alive?
If I hadn't been so eager,
and brought father back to the mansion myself,
would he still be alive?
Self-blame
can't bring the dead back to life.
Your Highness,
His Majesty has summoned you to the palace.
Did she say why?
It seems to be related to the prison.
I see.
Your Highness,
please take me with you.
I heard that
you and Shen Suhe went to the prison,
and Hao'er and his wife
were both injured.
Anyway,
he's a prince
who hasn't been convicted.
How dare you use private punishment?
Look,
the memorials against you
have piled up like a mountain.
I know you're eager to solve the case,
but being so reckless
is not your style.
Or
are you covering up
for Shen Suhe?
Your Majesty, please investigate thoroughly.
All of this
was done by me alone.
It has nothing to do with anyone else.
I am willing
to accept punishment.
I, Shen Suhe,
pay my respects to Your Majesty.
Regarding Shen Yi's death,
I have already
provided compensation as a Prime Minister.
Your brother Shen Subai
will also receive preferential treatment
if he continues to serve as an official.
Although Hao'er has been imprisoned,
you are still the princess consort.
How can you call yourself a commoner?
I humbly request Your Majesty
to grant me a divorce agreement.
I have already
informed you through Prince Yu.
Didn't he tell you?
Perhaps he
was too busy
to inform me.
I
cannot
approve this.
However,
my promise of reward remains valid.
If you've thought it through,
you can come to see me at any time.
This is my only request.
If Your Majesty doesn't allow it,
I will kneel in front of Your Majesty
and never get up.
Your Majesty's oral edict.
Your Majesty
has now approved the Shen
to divorce Prince Rui.
After the divorce agreement is drafted,
it will be sent to your residence.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Miss Shen,
I'm not criticizing you,
but why bother?
You should know that
Prince Yu has already taken the blame for you.
Why do you insist on kneeling?
Prince Yu?
What did Prince Yu do?
I'm sorry for my words.
This matter
is better not to mention.
If you have nothing else to do,
you can leave now.
Chief Eunuch
I have another question.
Please.
I saw that the Second Prince and the Fourth Prince
wore a white jade thumb ring
on the left thumb of them.
Do you know the origin of the ring?
Yes, I know.
In the year before last,
at the birthday banquet of the Empress Dowager,
His Majesty
had a batch of rings specially made.
Every prince, princess,
and imperial grandson
has one.
They should wear it for a whole year.
What?
Miss Shen,
you don't know about this?
I see.
Thank you for telling me.
So,
the person who killed me in the dream,
was he from the Imperial Clan?
Too many members of the Imperial Clan go to Lingguo Temple.
What's the reason
that he killed me?
Your Highness
Slow down.
Why are you here?
Did His Majesty give you a hard time?
Is it because of me?
Are you punished
because of me, right?
Don't flatter yourself.
It has nothing to do with you.
How could it have nothing to do with me?
This place
has nothing to do with you.
General Xiao,
although my subordinates
have been cleared of their names,
the mastermind
the real culprit
has not been brought to justice.
I feel I owe them,
that's why I spoke out against Your Majesty
and am willing to accept the punishment.
It really has nothing to do with you.
You should go.
Just go.
It turns out we were all fools.
It's clearly the villain's fault,
why are we the ones suffering?
Why?
Why are you here?
I...
I'm here to check on your wound.
Didn't I say
it had nothing to do with you?
Mu Jinghao and Ling Chuchu
were hurt by me,
but you took the blame for me.
How could I just leave you behind?
Thank you.
But
I remember I told you
that it's none of your business.
And I also told you
that I would repay
your kindness.
Your Highness.
I'll go and see if there's anything to eat.
I'll bring you some.
Why is she here?
Since
we picked you up from the palace,
she has been following us,
never leaving.
You were injured on the back,
and had a fever for two days and nights.
Miss Shen has been taking care of you.
By the way,
who did she meet in the palace?
What happened?
I only remember
after she entered the palace,
she knelt for a long time in front of His Majesty,
and finally got the divorce agreement.
Divorce agreement?
She divorced?
[This maid]
[why does she look so familiar?]
I, Shen Suhe,
pay my respects to Your Majesty.
Rise.
Don't be so formal.
Sit with me.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Minister Shen was suddenly killed.
His Majesty has already ordered
a thorough investigation into this matter.
Death cannot be brought back.
Don't be too sad.
After all,
the road ahead is still long.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I understand.
I summoned you here today
to inform you of something.
After much consideration,
I believe
you should be aware.
Last night, the Second Prince
suddenly hanged himself in prison.
Consort Ling
is in deep sorrow,
and remains unconscious.
Your Majesty
is worried about this.
How could the Second Prince suddenly...
Your Majesty has ordered to keep this a secret.
Although you and the Second Prince
have divorced,
all the things in Prince Rui's Mansion
have nothing to do with you.
You are young.
You should find a support
for your future.
Although Prince Yu
is a general,
he is more composed
than the Second Prince.
He can be a good choice.
You misunderstood me.
Prince Yu and I
are not what you think.
Don't worry.
I'm not
as conservative as those old people.
Men can have several wives.
Why should women
be faithful to one person?
Moreover,
our dynasty's laws
have long allowed women to remarry.
If you are really sincere,
I will speak for you and Prince Yu
in front of His Majesty.
As for those rumors,
just listen to them.
Don't care about them.
Prince is noble,
I never want to rely on him.
I
don't want to
interfere in the affairs outside the palace.
The huge harem
has made me headache enough.
But after all,
you are the daughter of Minister Shen.
Shen Residence has been in trouble,
I want to take care of you
for them.
Besides,
the Prime Minister is also your teacher.
If you
have any difficulties in the future,
you can come to me at any time.
No need for formalities.
You are so kind.
I'm so grateful.
It was not until Yuan'er was born
that I realized
as a mother,
for the sake of the child,
one can give up everything.
Empress Mother.
Yuan'er.
Your Highness.
Today,
I disturbed Her Majesty the Empress.
The Prince is more important.
I
will leave now.
Your Majesty,
I'll see Miss Shen off.
Yuan'er,
let me hug you.
Young Master,
someone just sent a message that
Miss is looking for you in a hurry.
She's waiting for you at the tea house.
Zhao, do you have something to tell me?
The one
who's been helping you all along
is Prince Yu,
right?
Sui'er,
what's the matter
that you called me here in such a hurry?
Prince Yu has just returned to the capital.
I've never met him before.
How can he help me?
Sui'er,
I know after the death of our teacher,
the Prime Minister's Residence is not as good as before.
If you need help,
I can help you at any time.
But my uncle,
you shouldn't be so close to him.
Brother Zhao, don't worry.
I promise you,
Prince Yu and I
are not what you think.
That's the best.
I'll go back first.
Your Highness,
isn't it cruel to Miss Shen?
I've given her a chance to choose,
but she chose
the wrong way.